Stu Coston

Digital Designer.

Profile

For the last 6 years I've worked as a project manager on \$2.3B worth of Government programs and a number of large scale construction projects. During this time, I fell in love with graphic and website design and development. I have been designing and developing digital experiences on the side for brands, businesses, and start-ups for about 5 years but I'm ready to take it full-time. A creative front-end developer at heart, my passion is constructing elegant, engaging, and easy-to-use websites through well-crafted code or popular CMSs.

Skills



Work History

Program and Contracts Manager 2012-2017
United States Air Force

Front-End Developer and Copywriter 2014-2017
Freelance

Founder - Digital Agency 2017-2019
Goby Creative

Education

United States Air Force Academy 2008-2012
Bachelor of Science
Systems Engineering

Defense Acquisition University 2016
Program Management Level 2

Experience

Leadership

Managed 25 person department overseeing \$800M+ of Government assets; awarded Large Team of the Quarter by Division Director

Led 9 person cross-functional team to on-time award of \$450M production contract for US Government and Foreign Militaries

Led \$17.5M test project with a 40 person team; developed a test operations schedule that challenged the status quo -- saved \$700K and 3 weeks to the project

Led 3 person team for procurement of an \$80M Information Technology services contract managing 100+ task pipeline; ranked #1/13 Officers by Senior Director

Scheduling

Aligned 6 separate schedules with 44 critical path tasks completed on time; ranked #1/11 Junior Officers on installation by Senior Director

Director of Operations for department of 72 people -- organized the department into teams of 3-5 and delegated 300+ task schedule for efficient contract transition

Cost Management

Prepared a 4 year forecast for a \$1.3B pilot training system -- built relationships with vendors and end users to understand funding requirements and presented requirements to leadership to secure funding

Forecasted funding and contract milestones for \$450M procurement; identified and wrote 50+ pages of requirements to scope future system purchases

Coordinated pricing for \$2.5M of change orders on \$26M construction project